Topical files 1
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Topical files 1
2.1.9.4
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1613
- Topical files 1, 2.1.9.4
  - E. J. (Jerry) Ade, 1968 June 27; 1 (Box 1613)
    - Note[PDF]: June 27, 1968; Dear Lowell: I came across this in my Explorers Club file a moment ago, 1
    - June 27, 1968; Dear Lowell: I came across this in my Explorers Club file a moment ago, 2
  - Alaska, 1961- 1969; 2 (Box 1613)
    - [Alaska, Lowell Thomas at microphone with another man], 1
    - [Alaska, Lowell Thomas at microphone], 2
    - [Alaska, People on stage gathered for a picture. Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas(?) at center], 3
    - [Alaska, People on stage gathered for a picture. Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas(?) in back, toward center], 4
    - [Alaska, Little boy sitting on Balto statue in central park, Lowell Thomas standing next to him], 5
    - [Alaska, Little boy sitting on Balto statue in central park, Lowell Thomas standing next to him], 6
    - [Alaska, Little boy sitting on Balto statue in central park, Lowell Thomas standing next to him], 7
    - [Alaska, Little boy sitting on Balto statue in central park, Lowell Thomas standing next to him], 8
    - [Alaska, Little boy sitting on Balto statue in central park, Lowell Thomas standing next to him], 9
  - American Emergency Committee for Tibetan Refugees (AECTR), 1962 - 1963; 3 (Box 1613)
    - Artist, 1
    - Verso: Artist; KKC, 1-verso
    - Carpet on loom, 2
    - Verso: Carpet on loom; KKC, 2-verso
    - A 9 x 12 dragon design carpet is weaving., 3
    - Verso: A 9 x 12 dragon design carpet is weaving. Darjeeling Self Help Centre; KKC, 3-verso
    - Small carpet weaving, 4
    - Verso: Small carpet weaving. Darjeeling Self Help Centre; KKC, 4-verso
    - [?] Pougdens, 5
    - Verso: [?] Pougdens; KKC, 5-verso
    - Dorji artist with his painting, 6
    - Verso: Dorji artist with his painting Self Help Centre-Darjeeling; KKC, 6-verso
    - Chanting prayers, 7
    - Verso: Chanting prayers; KKC, 7-verso
    - Tibetan Refugees at Dalhousie, 8
    - Verso: Tibetan Refugees at Dalhousie; KKC, 8-verso
  - Anniversary - 10 years on the air, 1940 September 30 - October 4; 4 (Box 1613)
    - New YorkNiles Trammell, Left, President of the National Broadcasting Company, Presents a Gold-Plated Microphone to Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Note: New YorkNiles Trammell, Left, President of the National Broadcasting Company, Presents a Gold-Plated Microphone to Lowell Thomas..., 2
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: People seated at a long table with microphones, Lowell Thomas toward center], 3
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: People seated at a long table with microphones, Lowell Thomas toward center], 4
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas seated at a table with Frances Ryan Thomas(?), talking with another man], 5
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas seated at a table with Frances Ryan Thomas(?), talking with two other men], 6
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas standing behind NBC microphones with another man], 7
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas holding NBC microphone, standing with two other men], 8
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas holding NBC microphone, standing with two other men], 9
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas behind table with microphones, shaking hands with another man], 10
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas standing between two men, smiling], 11
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas standing behind a table with NBC microphones], 12
    - [Celebrating 10 years on the air: Lowell Thomas standing behind table, talking into NBC microphone], 13
  - 50th anniversary (wedding) - Mr. and Mrs. Thomas, Alaska [color photographs], 1967; 5 (Box 1613)
    - Fifty years of--Then; Long ago on that South Sea Honeymoon, 1
    - Verso: Now (and in-between--all those quiet, placid years), 1-verso
    - Fifty years of--Then; Long ago on that South Sea Honeymoon, 2
    - Verso: Now (and in-between--all those quiet, placid years), 2-verso
    - Fifty years of--Then; Long ago on that South Sea Honeymoon, 3
    - Verso: Now (and in-between--all those quiet, placid years), 3-verso
  - Gene Anthony [includes color photographs], 1962- 1963; 6 (Box 1613)
    - [Artist (Gene Anthony) looking at painting of Frances Ryan Thomas], 1
    - [Artist (Gene Anthony) next to painting of Anne (?)], 2
    - [Artist (Gene Anthony) and Lowell Thomas holding portrait of woman], 3
    - Donald Douglas being painted by Gene Anthony, 4
    - Verso: Donald Douglas being painted by Gene Anthony 1962, 4-verso
    - [Artist (Gene Anthony) painting portrait of little girl], 5
    - [Artist (Gene Anthony) next to painting of Donald Douglas], 6
    - Donald Douglas & Donald Douglas Jr., 7
    - Verso: Donald Douglas & Donald Douglas Jr., 7-verso
    - Gene Anthony Portrait Painting; 320 Laguna Terrace Simi, California, 8
  - Army Air Force [includes color photographs], 1940 - 1966; 7 (Box 1613)
    - Note: Air Force Academy, 1
    - [Lowell Thomas at podium for the Airforce Academy], 2
    - [Men standing behind table at the Airforce Academy, Lowell Thomas at far right], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with two men in uniform from Airforce Academy], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas signing a paper for two men in uniform from Airforce Academy], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with two men in uniform from Airforce Academy], 6
  - Army Air Force Convalescent Center, undated; 8 (Box 1613)
    - Henry Stommel author of "Science of the Seven Seas", 1
    - Verso: Henry Stommel author of "Science of the Seven Seas", 1-verso
  - Aviation, 1952- 1975; 9 (Box 1613)
    - Donald W. Douglas-President & Board Chairman Douglas Aircraft Co., Inc., 1
    - Note[PDF]: Crews of the three round-the-world B-52 Stratofortresses and their flight commander, Major General Archie J. Old, Jr, 2
    - Crews of the three round-the-world B-52 Stratofortresses and their flight commander, Major General Archie J. Old, Jr, 3
    - For Immediate Release: Crew of the B-50 "Lucky Lady II," Photographed before the history-making flight, the crew members are pictured from left to right, 4
    - Note[PDF]: For Immediate Release: Crew of the B-50 "Lucky Lady II," Photographed before the history-making flight, the crew members are pictured from left to right..., 5
  - Baghdad (new file), 1944- 1947; 10 (Box 1613)
    - Courtyard American School for Boys, Baghdad, 1
    - Verso: Courtyard American School for Boys, Baghdad June 10, 1946, 1-verso
    - Courtyard American School for Boys, Baghdad, 2
    - Verso: Courtyard American School for Boys, Baghdad, June 10, 1946, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas in Baghdad], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas in Baghdad], 4
    - Buffles et Griffons de la Porte d'Ishtar a Babylone, 5
    - Verso: 18 July 46 Dear Lowell Thomas: A Russian Cossak friend in Baghdad made this in color as a gift for me, since I was so interested in Babylon..., 5-verso
    - Mohammed Sedig Pusho Taha (Sheikh of Kurds) Dr. Matthew [?] (Syracuse University) Capt Archie Roosevelt (Asst Mil. Attache, Teheran), 6
    - Verso: Mohammed Sedig Pusho Taha (Sheikh of Kurds) Dr. Matthew [?] (Syracuse University) Capt Archie Roosevelt (Asst Mil. Attache, Teheran), 6-verso
    - July 9, 1946 [Two women and three men looking at map], 7
    - Verso: July 9, 1946, 7-verso
    - The Garden of Eden Will Flower Again; New York.-Programming the development of agricultural and engineering courses at the University of Baghdad, 8
    - Note[PDF]: The Garden of Eden Will Flower Again; New York.-Programming the development of agricultural and engineering courses at the University of Baghdad, 9
    - The Garden of Eden Will Flower Again; New York.-Programming the development of agricultural and engineering courses at the University of Baghdad, 10
    - Note[PDF]: The Garden of Eden Will Flower; Again New York.-Programming the development of agricultural and engineering courses at the University of Baghdad, 11
    - The Garden of Eden Will Flower Again; New York.-Programming the development of agricultural and engineering courses at the University of Baghdad, 12
    - Note[PDF]: The Garden of Eden Will Flower Again; New York.-Programming the development of agricultural and engineering courses at the University of Baghdad, 13
    - Launch $15,000,000 Campaign for Postwar Work in College. Launching a campaign to raise $15,000,000 for the Near East Colleges to rehabilitate their facilities and expand their postwar work, 14
    - Note[PDF]: Launch $15,000,000 Campaign for Postwar Work in College. Launching a campaign to raise $15,000,000 for the Near East Colleges to rehabilitate their facilities and expand their postwar work, 15
    - Launch $15,000,000 Campaign for Postwar Work in College. Launching a campaign to raise $15,000,000 for the Near East Colleges to rehabilitate their facilities and expand their postwar work, 16
    - Note[PDF]: Launch $15,000,000 Campaign for Postwar Work in College. Launching a campaign to raise $15,000,000 for the Near East Colleges to rehabilitate their facilities and expand their postwar work, 17
    - Sam Pryor, Frank Mason, Hugh Gibson, 18
    - Verso: Sam Pryor, Frank Mason, Hugh Gibson July 9, 1946, 18-verso
    - July 9, 1946 [Lowell Thomas and two other men looking at map], 19
    - Verso: July 9, 1946
  - Banquet (ideas after Plaza party), 1941 April 29; 11 (Box 1613)
    - [Banquet. Ladies in dresses and men in suits near window], 1
    - [Banquet. Ladies in dresses posing for a picture near window with view of snowcapped mountains], 2
  - Barbecue fireplace fittings, 1938 September 1; 12 (Box 1613)
    - Campbell Foundry Co. Harrison, N.J. ["Horace Greeley Grill"], 1
    - Verso: Campbell Foundry Co. Harrison, N.J., 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: Dear Mr. Thomas: - A few Sundays ago we saw, in the Tribune, an article about your out of door parties, and it occurred to us that you might like to have a gadget made in our foundry..., 2
  - Bay State Films, 1947; 13 (Box 1613)
    - [Bay State Films:]Eastman 25 Projector, 1
    - Verso: Eastman 25 Projector, 1-verso
    - [Bay State Films:]Black + White + Color Duplications, 2
    - Verso: Black + White + Color Duplications, 2-verso
    - [Bay State Films:]Screening Room, 3
    - Verso: Screening Room, 3-verso
    - [Bay State Films:]Window from Sound Room to Recording Studio, 4
    - Verso: Window from Sound Room to Recording Studio, 4-verso
    - [Bay State Films:]Processing, 5
    - Verso: Processing, 5-verso
    - [Bay State Films:]Processing, 6
    - Verso: Processing, 6-verso
    - [Bay State Films:]Animation, 7
    - Verso: Animation, 7-verso
  - Larry Beck [color photograph], 1970; 14 (Box 1613)
    - Season's Greetings; Carol + Larry, 1
    - Note: Mr. + Mrs. Larry Beck c/o D.W. Loven [address], 2
  - Gertrude Bell [paintings], undated; 15 (Box 1613)
    - [Portrait of woman by Gertrude Bell (?) (Portrait of Gertrude Bell?)], 1
    - [Portrait of woman by Gertrude Bell (?) (Portrait of Gertrude Bell?)], 2
  - Victor Berge, 1951; 16 (Box 1613)
    - Exploring! [Victor Berge sitting at table], 1
    - Verso: Exploring!, 1-verso
    - Victor in tropical smoke amusing himself in Stockholm, 2
    - Verso: Victor in tropical smoke amusing himself in Stockholm, 2-verso
    - Victor greeting his guests with the Tahitian gesture of welcome, 3
    - Verso: Victor greeting his guests with the Tahitian gesture of welcome, 3-verso
    - Note: [Photocopy of Berge picture]The Master Pearler and adventurer Victor Berge now at 60 as peppy as ever Note! reverse picture!..., 4
    - Sture Floding, 5
    - Verso: [?] negative Picture no 21, 5-verso
    - Victor Berge, 6
    - Verso: Victor Berge, pictured at Stockholm, Sweden Nov. 51. Picture no 1, 6-verso
  - Victor Berge, 1952; 17 (Box 1613)
    - Victor Berge pearling in an atoll Lagoon of the South Seas "weighing his Baby" 1929., 1
    - Victor Berge "Skin Diving" in Stockholm 1951. Berge "Snow Diving" in his Home town Bollns, Hlsingland, 1952., 2
    - Victor Berge Diving for Pearl Shell in Pallawan Islands Philipines 1948/1949 with his own Patented Mask. Berges U.S, Patern of his Diving Mask., 3
    - Note[PDF]: Reinforced Plastic Pearling huggers for Berge's Patented Diving Mask to stow onboard his 160 ft. Pearl Diving Mother Ship. A White Mother of Pearl Shell., 4
  - Herb Bergman, 1981; 18 (Box 1613)
    - To my friend Lowell Thomas With best of respects. Sincerely, Herb Bergman, 1
    - Verso: To my friend Lowell Thomas With best of respects. Sincerely, Herb Bergman, Al-Khobar - K. of S.A. 1981 - August. Herb Bergman, 1-verso
  - Pat Billo [color photograph], 1974; 19 (Box 1613)
    - [Pat Billo standing by a fence], 1
  - Boeing, 1975; 20 (Box 1613)
    - [Boeing, Lowell Thomas sitting on a plane, holding a mask next to a woman], 1
    - [Boeing, Lowell Thomas sitting at a type writer], 2
  - Norman Bowen, 1957; 21 (Box 1613)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to Norman Bowen], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting next to Norman Bowen], 2
  - Bill Brumbaugh, undated; 22 (Box 1613)
    - Birthplace of Lowell Thomas World Traveler, and Author Also of Radio, TV and Cinerama Fame "So Long Until Tomorrow", 1
  - Robert Campbell, 1940s; 23 (Box 1613)
    - Campbell, Robert J. LTCOL FV885912 3 Jan 67, 1
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell in uniform], 2
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell in uniform], 3
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell in uniform], 4
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell in uniform], 5
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell in uniform], 6
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell in uniform], 7
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell in uniform], 8
  - C. Whitney Carpenter, 1939; 24 (Box 1613)
    - Egypt: River Nile, 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Esq; The Waldorf-Astoria; Park Avenue New York USA; Am arriving [?] New York Feb. 9th by S.S. Rex + go at once to Bedford Hills, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to another man, both in Egyptian garb], 2
    - [?] I [desert?] outside an old walled village 2 days from [Luait?] Kuwait, 3
    - Verso: [?] I [desert?] outside an old walled village 2 days from [Luait?] Kuwait, 3-verso
  - Rika Charmoz, undated; 25 (Box 1613)
    - Rika Charmoz [phone number], 1
    - Note: Rika Charmoz [phone number], 2
  - Dan Chase, 1941; 26 (Box 1613)
    - Camp [?] 1941 [?] Ballet in play July 18th Very [?] well and very [?] well [?], 1
    - Verso: Camp [?] 1941 [?] Ballet in play July 18th Very [?] well and very [?] well [?], 1-verso
  - Harry Chase (in Arab garb), circa 1918; 27 (Box 1613)
    - Mr. Chase-contact size block, 1
    - Verso: Mr. Chase-contact size block, 1-verso
    - Mr. H. A. Chase, chief camera man attached to the staff of Lowell Thomas during the Arabian campaign., 2
    - Verso: Mr. H. A. Chase, chief camera man attached to the staff of Lowell Thomas during the Arabian campaign., 2-verso
    - [Harry Chase in Arab garb], 3
    - Chase, Arab garb, squatting., 4
    - Verso: Chase, Arab garb, squatting., 4-verso
  - Chimo, circa late 1930s; 28 (Box 1613)
    - Proof #6551 Westminster K.C. Show Feb-11-1941 "Chimo", 1
  - Christmas [includes color photographs], 1969 -1978; 29 (Box 1613)
    - Note [Outside of Image Container]: ajihnlo hnlopai ihn lopal hnoljihn nlop ihn lopaj ajihn japol lopajihn ajihnlo hnlo hnlopai ihn lopal hn japol lopajihn ajihnlop ihn api, 1
    - Note [Inside of Image Container]: ajihnlop il n lopaj ajihn japol lopajihn hnlop ajihnlop japahiln a jihnlop ajihn japol [images 3-14 contained within], 2
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas(?)], 3
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas in a group picture], 4
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas on steps with Frances Ryan Thomas(?) and two other women], 5
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas(?)], 6
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at table], 7
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in chair(?)], 8
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thoams sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas], 9
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas standing with Frances Ryan Thomas], 10
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thoams sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas in front of sign that reads "The Village Inn: Ourty(?) Nelly's"], 11
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing in front of grand building (castle?)], 12
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing in front of flower arrangement], 13
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing], 14
    - [Christmas: Snowy road and house], 15
    - Merry Christmas '73 from The Callahans; Fifteen friends joined the Callahans on the Ohio and Mississippi Rivers, 16
    - Verso: Merry Christmas '73 from The Callahans; Fifteen friends joined the Callahans on the Ohio and Mississippi Rivers, 16-verso
    - Silent Night; Carroll and Bill Rickenbacker, 17
    - Channing Lowe Williams College; Carol Channing and Charles Lowe 1973, 18
    - Verso: Holiday Greetings from Our House to Your House; Carol Channing - Charles Lowe [address], 18-verso
    - and a Happy New Year! North Haven, Maine 1973, 19
    - Verso: Our very warmest regards to you both. Skied Alta last week + saw your old friend Alf but didn't meet him., 19-verso
    - Merry Christmas Our House to Your House; Rod and Barbara Lankler Andy, Doug, Greg & Steve, 20
    - Holiday Joy, 21
    - Verso: Happy New Year; Fran & Lowell. Christmas-getting a ski area open and shaken-down in time for the christmas crussh-are like oil and water!..., 21-verso
    - Dear Mr. Thomas, Thank you for your beautiful card of your own "Seven Wonders." We will treasure this, always!..., 22
    - Noel; Dee Dee Beck, 23
    - Verso: Rich and [Beck?] San Clemente ?, 23-verso
    - Holiday Joy; The Pryors, 24
    - [House behind bushes], 25
    - Holiday Greetings, 26
    - Verso: The Sawyers, 26-verso
  - Christmas [includes color photographs], 1972 - 1976; 30 (Box 1613)
    - God Bless You; The Billy Grahams, 1
    - Verso: God Bless You; The Billy Grahams, 1-verso
    - [Christmas: Baby], 2
    - Noel; Happy Holidays to you both! Love from the [?], 3
    - Sun Valley '73; Thanksgiving Greetings & Holiday Joy Gretchen & Don Fraser, 4
    - Merry Christmas Our House to Your House; The Treats, 5
    - Verso: Dear Mr. + Mrs. Thomas--We had marvelous reunion with Sonny. Reminisced about Lake Placid, Dartmouth, Tuckerman's Ravine, vacation in Pawling + the families..., 5-verso
    - Holiday Joy; Dears. South Sea trip was great Hope you have a Happy Holiday Love Frances, 6
    - St. Moritz Express-1973, 7
    - Mele Kalikimaka Hauoli Makahiki Hou Merry Christmas Happy New Year John and Laurie Parker, Holly, Jessica, 8
    - Verso: We look forward to seeing you after Christmas. My brother George and his new bride will be with us for the holidays, 8-verso
    - [Christmas: Lowell Thomas at a wedding ceremony], 9
  - Eddie Connellan, undated; 31 (Box 1613)
    - [Eddie Connellan: Statue of man with a beard], 1
    - [Eddie Connellan: Large group of people sitting around a bonfire], 2
  - Homer Croy [letter on back of photograph of Mary Pickford], undated; 32 (Box 1613)
    - Salting the Cattle Day; Lowell: I was sure 'nuff surprised Tuesday soir when I hear you begin to talk about Hollywood and Theda Bara, 1
    - Verso[PDF]: Salting the Cattle Day; Lowell: I was sure 'nuff surprised Tuesday soir when I hear you begin to talk about Hollywood and Theda Bara, 1-verso
  - Dalai Lama, undated; 33 (Box 1613)
    - Tibetan Cultural Center Building in the Process of Construction; Side View, 1
    - Verso: Tibetan Cultural Center Building in the Process of Construction; Side View, 1-verso
    - [Dai Lama and group of little boys], 2
    - [Dai Lama: Grand Tibetan building], 3
  - Major General Herbert Darque [Documents pertaining to Air Force Air Defense System Testing; Containing maps, diagrams, and photographs [some originals with copies]; Front and back of pages number a total of 25 [missing pages 1/2 and 21/22], 1932- 1941; 34 (Box 1613)
    - Note[PDF]: Page 3: Plate 1. Area covered by test and course information must follow to make interception possible., 1
    - Note[PDF]: Page 4: 8. Sighting the plane.-The plane, if approaching overland, is first sighted by one of hundreds of civilian observers spotted five to eight miles apart throughout the test sector, 2
    - Note[PDF]: Page 5: Plate 2. Observation Post at Sands Point Club, Long Island (Courtesy of Life); Plate 3. Chart of two toll centers, showing lines of flow of messages through local switch-boards[Original page and plates attached], 3
    - Note[PDF]: Page 6: 11. Filter board plotting.- The "raw" information from the observer is received by a "plotter" sitting at the filter board. The plotter, a woman volunteer, has individual mouthpiece and earphones[Original page and plate from page attached], 4
    - Note[PDF]: Page 7: Plate 5. Old Filter Board, New York Information Center. [Original plate attached], 5
    - Note[PDF]: Page 8: 12. Interpretation.- A filterer standing behind the plotter waits until three or more reports have been received. Discrepancies as to fact are eliminated by weeding out details which vary from the bulk fo the reports on any item..., 6
    - Note[PDF]: Page 8: 12. Interpretation.- A filterer standing behind the plotter waits until three or more reports have been received. Discrepancies as to fact are eliminated by weeding out details which vary from the bulk fo the reports on any item[Orginal plate from page attached], 7
    - Note[PDF]: Page 9: 14. Transmission.- On a balcony overlooking the filter board are tellers, one for each toll center show on the board. Each has a telephone headset and can see clearly each move on the board[Original plate from page attached], 8
    - Note[PDF]: Verso: Page 10: 17. Decision.- On a mezzanine balcony overlooking the operations board are the controller, who acts for or is commanding officer for the region[Original plate from page attached], 9
    - Note[PDF]: Page 11: Plate 9. Diagramatic cut out of new Information Center in New York, 10
    - Note[PDF]: Verso: Page 12: Plate 10. New Operations board, status board and seaward board in New York Center. [Original plate attached], 11
    - Note[PDF]: Page 13: 18. Intercept orders.- Upon ascertaining the strength, location, direction and speed of an enemy flight in his region the controller orders into the air from the most logical airdrome in his region pursuit of sufficient strength to effect the interception...[Orginal plate from page attached], 12
    - Note[PDF]: Verso: Page 14: by taking over the task of navigation for them. Intercept tellers are designated to relay to the intercept officer the military intelligence displayed upon the filter boards, 13
    - Note[PDF]: Page 15: more time than the fuel capacity of the pursuit would permit. The pursuit therefore attempts to effect interception on a course as nearly head-on as possible[Orginal plates from page attached], 14
    - Note[PDF]: Verso: Page 16: 26. The Command Post.- At the New York Information Center is a command post for the Commanding General, First Interceptor Command. At this command post is an operations board[Original plate from page attached], 15
    - Note[PDF]: Page 17: Plate 15. Diagram of Command, First Interceptor Command. As indicated, the same general organization exists in the 2nd, 3rd and 4th. [Original plate attached], 16
    - Note[PDF]: Verso: Page 18: Section III; The Mechanics of the System; 29. Use of the Telephone System.- The existence of the American Telephone and Telegraph Company, with its network of local and long lines which have no parallel in anywhere else in the world, 17
    - Note[PDF]: Page 19: Plate 17. Discs placed on map for selection of observation posts after marking of telephones [Orginal plate attached], 18